Borensvägen 1 120 52 Årsta

Phone: 0709-180015 E-mail: mia.sjolin@gmail.com

LANGUAGES

Swedish (native) English (fluent) French (basics)

VOLUNTEER WORK

IT-support and homework help for the organization *Individuell Människohjälp*. I volunteered evenings in the public library. As IT-support I helped inexperienced computer users. Other evenings I helped students from high school and from SFI with their homework.

PUBLICATION

My master thesis in speech and language therapy resulted in an article that was published. Norrelgen F, Fernell E, Eriksson M, Hedvall Å, Persson C, Sjölin M, Gillberg *C, Kjellmer L, (2014)* Children with autism spectrum disorder who do not develop phrase speech in the preschool years. Autism 19: 934-943. (http://journals.sagepub. com/doi/abs/10.1177/13 62361314556782

OTHER

Certified Scrum Master (https://www.scrum.org/user/332452)
Drivers license

WORK EXPERIENCE

Frontend developer, Telia

2019-now

At Telia I work in team Context, which are responsible for sitewide resources, such as navigation, general UI components, analytics. We work close together with the content editors, as we create editable components to our CMS which they use to build the site.

IT-consultant, Academic Work

2018-2019

After finishing Academys accelerated learning program, I started working as a consultant at Academic Work. I got an assignment at Telia and was recruited by them a year later.

Speech- and language therapist,

2013-2018

Röstkonsulten

Worked with focus on children with speech- and language disorders as well as with children with selective mutism. My responsibilities were investigation, diagnose, treatment and informing relatives. Apart from working directly with patients it was also included to inform/advice/cooperate with other professions working close to the child, and an obligation to keep medical records.

Consultant, Academic work

2010-2012

While studying to become a speech and language therapist, I worked part time as a consultant. I worked mostly for Philips Respironics, where I handled their customer service which meant dealing with orders, send invoices, answer the phone and handle offers.

I also worked at Nordea as a switchboard operator.

Receptionist på Ibis Hotel Arlanda 2007-2009

Started out working in the hotel restaurant and was then offered a permanent employment as night receptionist. I worked nights for 10 months, and thereafter I started working days instead. Apart from handling the front desk I also drove guests to and from the airport.

Phone: 0709-180015 E-mail: mia.sjolin@gmail.com

EDUCATION

Accelerated learning program in Java, Academy	2018
Speech and language program, Karolinska institutet (240hp)	2009-2013
Legal overview course, Uppsala Universitet (15 hp)	2008
Parts from pharmacist program, Uppsala Universitet (60hp)	2006-2007
French, one semester of studies in Montpellier	2005
Pedagogy A, Uppsala Universitet (30hp)	2004

OTHER EDUCATION

Supervisor training. In 2015 I attended a supervisor training for speech and language therapists in Karolinska Institutet, and have then supervised two speech and language students during their internship period in the course of speech and language disorders in children.

Further education in selective mutism. Has through my job at Röstkonsulten taken two full-day courses in selective mutism.

REFERENCES

I will gladly send references if desired.